https://www.candlewarmers.com/privacypolicy

THE LAST DAY TO PLACE RETAIL ORDERS AND RECEIVE THEM BEFORE CHRISTMAS IS DECEMBER 15.
FREE SHIPPING ON RETAIL ORDERS OVER $30!
50% OFF OUR LIMITED EDITION HOLIDAY FRAGRANCE PACK! USE PROMO CODE MERRY!
SAVE 20% WITH BUNDLE BUILDER!
Subscribe
*By clicking 'Subscribe', you agree to receive marketing emails from Candle Warmers and our Terms of Use.
Subscribe
View:
Privacy Policy
Candle Warmers Etc, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy and using technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Candle Warmers Etc. web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Candle Warmers Etc. web site you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Candle Warmers Etc. collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, zip code and telephone number.
Candle Warmers Etc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of web sites you choose to link to from Candle Warmers Etc. so that you can understand how those web sites collect, use and share your information. Candle Warmers Etc. is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on web sites outside of Candle Warmers Etc.
USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Candle Warmers Etc. does not sell, rent, or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Candle Warmers Etc. keeps track of the web sites and pages our customers visit within the Candle Warmers Etc. web site in order to determine what services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within the Candle Warmers Etc. web site.
Candle Warmers Etc. web site will not disclose your personal information without notice, except if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Candle Warmers Etc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Candle Warmers Etc.; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Candle Warmers Etc., or the public.
SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Candle Warmers Etc. secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Candle Warmers Etc. secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as credit card number) is transmitted to other web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT
Candle Warmers Etc. will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect the company and customer feedback. Candle Warmers Etc. encourages you to periodically review this policy to be informed of how Candle Warmers Etc. is protecting your information.
CONTACT INFORMATION
Candle Warmers Etc. welcomes your comments regarding the Privacy Policy. If you believe that Candle Warmers Etc. has not adhered to this policy, please contact us using our Contact Us page. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
HYPERTEXT LINKS
Candle Warmers Etc. has included hypertext links to this web site. These hypertext links are not under the control of Candle Warmers Etc. Accordingly, Candle Warmers Etc. cannot make any representation concerning the quality, safety, or the content of these sites nor can or does the fact that Candle Warmers Etc. has included any hypertext link, serve as an endorsement by Candle Warmers Etc. of any of these hypertext links. Candle Warmers Etc. is providing this web site, the content thereof, the listings, and the hypertext links only as information to the public.
COPYRIGHT NOTICE
This web site, including but not limited to the text, design, content, photographs, (video and audio), is protected by copyright as a collective work or compilation under U.S. copyright law and other applicable statutes and regulations. You are required to adhere to this and all other copyright notices or restrictions of this web site.
You may not copy, reproduce, publish, perform, modify, create derivative works, or in any way exploit any part of this web site.
ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS
By using this web site, you signify your acceptance of and agreement to Candle Warmers Etc. Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS POLICY, PLEASE DISCONTINUE SERVICE. Your continued use of Candle Warmers Etc.'s web site following posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
CONNECT WITH US
Follow us on our social channels or sign up to receive Candle Warmer emails.
Submit
By clicking 'Subscribe', you agree to receive marketing emails from Candle Warmers and agree to our Terms of Use & Terms of Sale and Privacy Policy.
